<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Covid19 Self Check</string>
    <string name="this_app_questions">This application contains questions list to check your physical condition</string>
    <string name="check_now">Check Your Condition Now</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back to Home</string>
    <string name="question">Questions</string>
    <string name="q1">Did you encounter any one of these symptoms:\n\n
        - Severe difficulty breathing (Breathing very quickly or talking by words)\n
        - Severe chest pain  \n
        - Difficulty waking up  \n
        - Feeling confused  \n
        - Unconsciousness</string>
    <string name="q2">Did you encounter any one of these symptoms:\n\n
- Difficulty breathing during rest\n
- Difficulties on talking caused by difficulty breathing\n
- Worsening symptoms of current chronic disease caused by difficulty breathing</string>
    <string name="q3">Did you encounter any one of these symptoms:\n\n
- Fever\n
- Coughing\n
- Sneezing\n
- Sore throat\n
- Difficulty breathing</string>
    <string name="q4">Did you encounter any symptoms after travelling to overseas within 14 days? (China, Italy, Iran, South Korea, France, Spain, Germany, USA) or to affected cities (Jakarta, Bali, Solo, Yogyakarta, Pontianak, Manado, Bandung etc)?</string>
    <string name="q5">Were you treating or having close contact with someone infected with COVID-19 (probable or confirmed) when they are sick (ever, coughing, sneezing, or sore throat)?</string>
    <string name="q6">Were you having close contact with anyone that recently went overseas within 14 days who are sick (ever, coughing, sneezing, or sore throat)?</string>
    <string name="conclusion">Conclusion</string>
    <string name="con_danger">These symptoms requires immediate medical attention. You need to contact nearest hospital, or go to the nearest Emergency Unit.</string>
    <string name="con_isolate">To prevent the spread of the disease, we kindly ask anyone with these symptoms (fever, coughing, sneezing, sore throat, or difficulty breathing) to remain at home for at least 14 days. You are advised NOT to go to public spaces, stay at home and do not receive any guests. You are also advised to call local Covid 19 Task Force, please do not go to hospital, ER, or clinic. If your condition worsens please seek medical attention immediately.</string>
    <string name="con_good">You are very likely NOT infected with COVID-19, but you are advised to stay at home. Infection may be caused by virus other than COVID-19, so COVID-19 testing is unnecessary. Even so, avoid going out if possible. Your symptoms will go away with enough resting and eating.\n\nIf you are facing any symptoms or having new info about your health, you can open this app again.</string>

    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Bahasa Indonesia</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>